Gentle-hearted gay man Genichi Hatano
and his crush,
Saku Sakuta,
find themselves growing closer
under the same roof.
I support you
in pretending to be her parent.
The "Parent-Child Contract"
previously made with Hotaru
now has Saku's name too.
Koito…
I liked him so much back in middle school.
Genichi finally puts an end to the regrets
lingering from his first love.
I bought a house with my partner.
Maybe the partnership stuff
should come first?
As both of their feelings align,
they start searching for a home.
- Are we buying it or not?
- We are. Let's buy it!
I want to know how you and your partner
bought your home, Koito.
And the required documents.
And the required documents
that you needed for the loan.
Got it!
I think I kept them all together,
so I’ll look for it later.
Really? Thanks.
My partner
is looking forward to meeting you.
Wait.
So you two are dating now?
Things escalated quickly, huh?
Ah, yeah. Well…
Okay, talk to you later. Bye.
How’d it go?
Next time, when we
go over to Koito’s place,
he said he'll show us
the loan documents and stuff.
Okay, we can talk about that
when that time comes.
About the partnership,
we need to make an appointment
and go to the city office.
Do you have any off days for work?
And I’d like to meet your parents too.
Are you really okay with this?
- Huh?
- The partnership with me and all that…
It just makes things easier
when you’re renting a place
or getting a mortgage.
It proves our relationship is legitimate.
That’s not what I meant.
- Are you planning for a breakup soon?
- Oh, no.
- I thought you wanted a "clamp".
- Yes, I do.
- A "clamp" in the form of a house.
- Okay, then.
Let’s call your parents.
Sorry I kept it from you.
That’s everything Tomoe told me.
Isn’t she being super selfish? My mom.
It's getting on my nerves.
It's all talk, saying she loves me.
- What are you doing?
- They expire today.
They’re safe to eat raw that period.
If you cook them,
they’ll last a bit longer.
- What?
- Yeah.
Whatever, I feel like stress-eating.
Oh! Two yolks!
I'm sure something good
is going to happen!
Because it’s a double yolk?
Yeah. When you get a double yolk,
or when you see someone
with a bouquet walking around,
something lucky happens after.
- Right…
- You don’t seem to believe me.
Perfect!
Nicely taken.
Hey,
you can clock out a bit early today.
Thank you.
Is something going on?
My mom is coming to Tokyo from Hokkaido.
Think of taking care of your parents
as part of your job
while you and they are still around.
While they are still around?
Even the boar that died
had way too much energy
and was kind of a nuisance.
Yeah.
Being alive also means
you could die anytime.
- Oh, how lovely!
- What?
I'm Hatano’s mother.
Thank you for looking after my son.
I’m Inokashira, the landlady.
Do you do art?
It's from quite a long time ago, though.
May I have a look?
Oh my.
It’s interesting.
This kind of… fantasy creature.
Isn't that right?
Thank you. Anyway, if you'd excuse me.
What fantasy?
You need to knock
three times, then bow,
and say, "Excuse me."
MOCK INTERVIEW FOR CLASS 4
Wait until they tell you to sit.
Okay.
- Don't give me "okay".
- Okaaay.
HOTARU KUSUNOKI
Here.
High school brochures
that I think might suit you.
You really need to decide soon!
- I’m going to live how I want from now on.
- What?
Like how my mom collects those keychains.
I’ll do whatever I want too.
- Such as?
- I’ll figure that out as I go.
- Huh?
- Well, if you'd excuse me.
Wait!
Hatano’s mother is coming today.
What? So, you two are officially together?
This is like greeting the in-laws, right?
Uh, well…
‪I guess so.
When did you fall for him?
- Huh?
- What do you like about him?
I'm the interviewer here, mind you?
Oh?
- I wrapped up work early.
- Ah, thank you.
Your mom’s here, right? Should I hide?
No, it’s fine.
Just please don’t make things complicated.
What do you mean?
You know, the whole
pretending-to-be-your-dad thing.
Oh, and the 30 million yen matter.
Okay.
Please, I beg you
Remember those days
Coming!
- Welcome back!
- I'm back.
It’s been a while.
I could hear you all the way out.
Nice to meet you. I’m Sakuta.
You must be the one…
And she is?
- How does it taste?
- It's great.
- Do you like it too?
- Yes, very.
I'm so glad to hear that!
- Eat as much as you like!
- Aren't you glad?
I am.
Such wonderful neighbors you have.
I feel like I'm the daughter here.
Age-wise, okay?
Then, from my perspective,
she's like my granddaughter?
By the way,
we’re going to the city office
together, Sakuta and I.
To apply
for the partnership certificate, yes?
You know about it?
Of course.
Are you two going to live together here?
We’re thinking about buying a place.
Yes, together.
That’s wonderful!
But what about the property agency?
Should I come along?
How old do you think I am?
Someone Hatano knows
is quite knowledgeable.
Next time, we’ll visit their place
and learn from them.
It's Koito.
Koito?
Oh! From middle school?
Your friend, yes?
You remember well.
- I want to come too.
- What?
Regarding Sakuta's parents,
maybe I could meet and greet them once
was what I was thinking.
They weren't around since I was born.
- Is that how it is?
- Yes.
Though, I get why you'd be curious…
You really do look like him.
- What?
- Ko from 3Happy.
- Who's that?
- Oh, come on!
It's this I'm talking about!
Haven’t you heard
of Three Steps to a Happy Ending?
In short, 3Happy.
It’s a boys' love manga, actually.
Two guys quit their toxic jobs,
use their meager severance
and unemployment money to travel,
and somehow go from rock bottom
to totally in love and a happy ending.
I couldn’t stop swooning!
‪See?
This is Ko.
Don’t you think he looks similar?
Really?
He does.
Right? You think so too?
So, try smiling a little like him.
Huh?
You look just like him!
Oh, whatever shall I do?
There’s this line I want him to say.
This is Iwai. There’s a scene
where Iwai and Ko
hug each other.
See? Over here.
‪YOU FINALLY SAID IT.
- So, why don’t you pretend to be Iwai
- What?
and hug each other here?
Come on now.
Don't be shy! Go on.
- Get a little closer. Snuggle up more!
- We're not doing it.
What's the harm? You're such a spoilsport.
- What?
- Oh? Hotaru.
Are you interested too?
Hey, wanna go
to the signing event together?
- What signing event?
- Ah… So that’s why you came.
Might as well since I'm here, you know.
Besides…
I also had to stop by the hospital.
- The hospital?
- They say I don't have much time left.
It seems I’m going to die.
What?
I was given a terminal diagnosis.
I have four months left.
Well, I’m going to get it checked
at the hospitals here too,
but the outlook isn't great.
But hey, you don’t need to worry
about any of that.
Your dad is around, after all.
Soon,
I’ll be moving into a local facility
where my friends are.
I find it hard to believe.
Even I'm shocked.
- Is that right?
- Surprisingly calm, huh?
I am worried, though.
It’s fine. Don’t worry about me.
Just leave me be.
I’d feel bad if you fussed over me.
I’m not exactly young anymore.
I'm somewhat…
prepared for it.
Oh my!
How reassuring!
VOICEMAIL SERVICE
No new messages.
Shouldn't you be staying with her?
She told me to leave her be.
She’s a stubborn one.
Once she proposes something,
she won’t listen.
Ah…
Only "ah" from you?
I was thinking "like mother, like son".
Shine
We shall shine together
I think so too.
- Did she always like it?
- What?
Did your mom always like
boys' love manga, that is.
Oh, no. I was surprised.
Romance between guys…
I thought she couldn’t handle it.
Really?
When I was 20,
I told my mom about my sexuality.
She cried.
She looked so distressed…
so it was a surprise.
Well, manga isn’t reality.
Yeah.
I'm done filling the forms.
Partnership certificate,
confirmation form, card application…
Wait.
What's this?
It's for including a child’s name
if we have one.
Are you considering Hotaru?
Yes…
If Hotaru hadn’t been a part of this,
I'm sure
none of this would have happened.
Yes.
Ah, hey!
Stop it, Chan! Ah, Chasu…
Don't do that.
‪Come on…
- Hello?
- Sorry for calling so late.
Is something up?
This Saturday…
That pizza place you told me about.
Wanna go there together?
Calm down, guys.
I’ve been kind of busy lately.
Got it. Alright, maybe another time then.
Okay.
U-Um--
Calm down, buddy!
- What are you doing?
- Sorry, can you help…
- Careful…
- Take this.
Hey, now!
- Slowly now…
- Oof.
Okay!
Everything is alright now.
HOKKAIDO SOUVENIR
Okay, now.
Don’t make things complicated, okay?
Koito’s partner will be there too.
I know!
- Welcome!
- Thanks for having us.
- Please come in!
- Okay.
Nice to meet you.
This is my partner, Ryogo Yagura.
And this is Hatano, Sakuta,
and Hotaru Kusunoki.
Thank you for inviting us.
Here, if you'd like.
Thank you! I’ll make some tea.
Thank you.
Please feel free to make yourself at home.
Is there anything I can help with?
Oh, don't worry about it!
The kitchen is messy.
Sorry.
Have a drink if you'd like.
- It's a nice place.
- I know, right?
We stretched ourselves hard.
Places are crazy expensive these days, no?
But when you consider the future,
you'd want one, right?
Especially for people like us.
And this. For the loan,
you'd need the partnership certificate…
We’re going to the city office soon.
- Oh, prior?
- Yeah.
That makes explaining
various things easier.
Sounds good.
And this is the notarized contract.
What's that?
It’s like a super contract
that protects our future.
Have it drafted by a legal professional
and file it at the city office.
It's going to cost time, effort,
and quite a sum of money, though.
This document here says
we can live together as a family.
And here, it says if something happens
to either of us,
the other can take care
of living arrangements and property.
Without this, if one of you
were to pass away,
you can’t leave your property or assets
to the other person.
Marriage would make this unnecessary.
That’s really important, huh?
Party A and Party B
are considered equivalent
to a de facto married couple
living in a shared household.
- Kinda sounds like something I wrote once.
- What?
It's nothing.
"Article 5, Living Rules."
You can also write rules
the both of you have agreed on together.
I see…
"Until both Party A and Party B
have finished bathing,
neither parties may use the futon."
Oh, I see how it is with you guys…
"Party B may not use
more than half of the eggs
in the refrigerator
to make hard-boiled eggs?"
I don't get it.
I’m party A, this person is party B.
I’d go out and buy a pack of eggs.
The one with ten.
And this person turns them all
into boiled eggs.
Without asking!
Boiled eggs are the best for working out,
and they keep you full and all that.
But, you know,
some days I want a fried egg,
or egg on rice, or a rolled omelet,
eggs benedict, an omelet,
or even poached eggs…
If you had to eat boiled eggs every day,
wouldn't you get sick of it?
Don't you agree?
- Somewhat.
- Even this morning, right?
I thought I’d make a fried egg,
so I cracked one open, but it was boiled.
All of them!
So that was why the kitchen sink
was covered in eggshells…
What do you think?
Since you guys are here,
I want to get a third-party opinion.
- What opinion?
- Well, you see…
the "half" rule was kind of vague.
Sometimes you don’t use
any eggs at all, Ryogo.
And when I made many boiled eggs,
there were times you didn't say anything…
Just because I was silent, does that mean
it’s okay to break our promise?
What matters more? Me or the boiled eggs?
Both.
Ask whatever you need from him here on.
Sorry about this.
- What?
- No way.
Really?
You should chase after him, Koito.
- Huh?
- Quick!
- Will they be okay?
- They'll be fine.
Ah, he caught up.
‪I can buy more eggs
‪if that's what you want.
I hope everything’s okay.
‪CHAN
‪CHASU
HOKKAIDO SOUVENIR
Looking for a nice place?
NICE PROPERTIES AVAILABLE!
Find me and this little guy a place,
a place where things feel right,
a place where I can be reborn
as a better person.
- Understood.
- Do such places exist?
Whether you believe me or not…
that’s up to you, sir.
That was a joke, really.
There’s no way I’d believe that!
Ah! It's a tortoise!
I don't think so.
It's definitely a turtle!
It's a tortoise.
It's a turtle, for sure!
A bird's legs…
Two, huh?
I wonder if a house
really can act as a "clamp"?
They’ll make up quickly, I’m sure.
You think so?
I'm back.
What?
Huh?
Where's Dora?
Even at this hospital…
It seems I really have…
until March!
Oh dear…
INOKASHIRA APARTMENTS
- Hello!
- Um!
What do you think this looks like?
Cute little flamingos!
Welcome back. Have you seen the tortoise?
What tortoise?
It seems to have gone missing
from Hatano’s place.
Oh my!
Found it?
I searched that area already,
but it isn't there.
- Found it?
- No.
I see. Same here.
If you see a double-yolk egg…
or see someone with a bouquet,
good things happen.
- What's that about?
- The landlady told me that.
I had a double-yolk egg the other day.
Everything will be fine.
Thanks.
It wasn't in the yard too.
Is that so?
You'll find it in no time.
Don't you think so too?
It'll be alright!
Oh, this!
At Suginomori Zoological & Botanical Park,
there was a contest
to design the mascot character.
That was ages ago though,
but I actually won a special prize,
and it ended up as a keychain.
Is that how it was?
It’s charming and cute.
What's the drawing of?
It’s a Tokyo bird, the black-headed gull.
The mascot is a gull shaped like Tokyo.
A gull, you say?
Gull, huh?
Now that you mention it…
Although for a gull,
it has a few too many legs, no?
I'm ashamed,
but the fact that birds have two legs
is something I only realized today.
- That's a flamingo.
- A flamingo, indeed.
I drew while carefully observing it.
And then all kinds of things
started to become clear.
It’s really fun!
Please fill out this lost property report.
Okay.
Ah, Mr. Ichigaya.
Mr. Hatano.
- Hello.
- What's the matter?
My tortoise disappeared.
- A tortoise?
- Yeah.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
I'll take my leave now.
Tortoise, huh?
Genichi Hatano?
Look forward to it! I'm gonna hang up now.
Alrighty.
HAPPY STORE
SAKU
- He’s not picking up.
- Perhaps he's busy.
This is my first time doing
something like this.
How do I put it?
Going against the flow?
Whether a relationship is starting
or ending,
I usually let it play out.
Isn’t that a good thing?
- Well then,
- What?
I'll need to do prep work before going
to the property agency,
as well as many other things.
- Um, is it regarding your condo?
- Yes.
I'd like to go to the property agency too.
Pardon?
Please come back!
I’ll limit myself to three…
no, five boiled eggs a day.
So, please!
Come on, Super Contract!
You’re taking the afternoon off today,
right, Hatano?
Yes, that's right.
Are you going somewhere with your mom?
It's for something else.
What’s wrong?
If you had known the boar
was going to die,
what would you have done for it?
I guess I'd pet it a lot,
smile at it, maybe sing…
or dance?
Words don’t reach animals, right?
So,
I’d do anything to show them I’m grateful.
Family register… Driver’s license…
Sakuta!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
- Shall we go?
- Yes.
Um… Are you really, truly okay with this?
- Are you chickening out?
- Yes, I am.
You’re the one who said we should do it.
But a partnership
is like getting married, right?
I don’t really think of it as marriage.
- What?
- We have to submit it!
Well, even if we do,
things rarely go smoothly for couples
like us, so it's just for the sake of it.
- That’s very procedural.
- It's important, no?
Hey, mind if we stop here?
Not at all.
So, are those two…
- getting along well?
- Huh?
Genichi and Sakuta.
Yes, very. All things considered,
they're lovey-dovey all the time.
Really?
They just can’t hide
their lovey-dovey vibes, both of them.
Is that how it is?
Really now…
When I said, "We’re here to submit
a partnership registration,"
didn’t they make a weird face?
You’re overthinking it.
Are you really, really,
really sure about this?
You're being persistent.
- Sorry for the wait.
- Yes.
Please wait a little more over there.
THREE STEPS TO A HAPPY ENDING
Ms. Umou,
let’s sign lots and get everyone excited!
Do people even want my autograph?
Of course!
After all,
things like a "Happy Ending" and such,
when there are so many people
in the world who aren’t happy,
it feels a bit shallow…
- I'm taking it now.
- Set it to burst mode, okay?
- Burst mode.
- Yes.
Got it.
How's this?
Perfect!
Thanks!
What got you into boys' love manga?
When Genichi…
told me he was gay,
I thought I'd try learning about it.
Of course, I read proper books
with words too, you know.
But in the middle of all that…
I discovered boys’ love manga.
After reading all sorts of them,
I got totally hooked!
And now 3Happy is my favorite.
So, that's how it is.
Do you have something you like, Hotaru?
It's a secret.
If it’s a secret,
that means you do have one.
First, regarding the partnership system,
please allow me explain it again.
This system
is for couples where both, or either one,
identify as a sexual minority.
As life partners to each other,
they respect each other's rights,
continuously support one another,
and promise to live together.
Only such couples
are able to register under this system.
- Okay.
- We'll start with identity verification.
Mr. Genichi Hatano, please show your ID.
Hatano!
Ah, sorry.
Are you okay?
I don’t know. I’m kind of scared.
Scared of what?
I’m feeling so happy, it's scary.
Sorry, please continue.
Please move forward and close the gap.
Oh my God!
I’m so glad I’m alive!
It’s like getting to meet God.
And I’m not even dead yet.
- Oh dear me! What do I do!
- Please calm down.
Sorry.
If you dissolve the partnership or move,
you'll need to return the certificate.
Do you want an acceptance certificate
for the card?
Yes, please.
Very well. By presenting
this card or certificate,
you’ll be able to access
various administrative services.
You can use it for public housing,
childcare, welfare,
and more hospitals are starting
to accept it too, so feel free to use it.
Okay!
Now, let’s check the documents.
Here you go.
Alright. We’ll issue the certificate,
so please wait a moment.
Thank you!
Are you really, really, really, truly
okay with this?
You're really annoying, okay?
Calling a house a "clamp"…
is honestly kind of just talk.
Even if it’s just talk or a lie…
if you truly believe it,
it will become real.
‪Okay.
There you have it.
- Hello.
These are for you.
I appreciate it.
May I please have your autograph?
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Could we shake hands?
Yes, if you don’t mind…
- Um…
- Yes?
My son…
He's gay.
When my son came out to me,
telling me he was gay,
I cried, thinking
he was such a poor thing.
As you know…
the world is harsh to people like him.
But I tried to come to terms with it
in my own way,
and in front of my son,
I wanted to be a good mom.
Still…
I couldn’t fully be at ease.
I always believed that two men
couldn’t truly be happy together.
I was a firm believer of that.
But look at Iwai and Ko.
They’re so happy together, aren’t they?
And that’s when it hit me!
No matter who you fall in love with,
people can be happy.
So, even my son
is by no means unhappy.
Something as obvious as that
is what I've only just realized.
From the bottom of my heart…
I'm really…
I'm so grateful to you!
H-How is he, really?
- What do you mean?
- Is your son happy?
Well…
It seems he is! Isn't that right?
Yes. Incredibly so.
A happy ending?
Yes. I’d say it’s a happy ending for me!
Is that so?
If that's the case,
that’s good to hear!
Yes.
Alright, I’m taking it now…
Three, two, one!
Looks good.
U-Um, could we try a different pose?
Sure!
Let’s jump, Sakuta.
- Why?
- Ready, set, go!
Smile!
- Okay.
- Ready, set, go!
Nice!
Smile, okay?
Ready, set, go!
So, you’ve decided to believe in it?
None of your business.
I just really need something
to latch onto right now.
I recommend one place.
It’s old, but pets are allowed,
and the landlord is a really nice person…
Are you sure about that?
Have a look.
Hello.
Hello!
- Uh…
- This is Mr. Yoshida.
He wants to consult you, Mr. Okabe.
Welcome. Please have a seat.
Are you looking for a house?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Please give me a moment.
What kind of house are you looking for?
Well, one that can act as a "clamp".
- Huh?
- What?
- Really?
Wait, is that a trend now?
- I've heard about it before too.
- Is it a trend?
- I might have started the trend.
- What?
I suggested to someone
that if they wanted to stay together,
perhaps they would need a "clamp".
After hearing that,
they proposed buying a house
for their partner.
Does that person wear glasses?
- Do they own a dog?
- Do they sing?
Uh…
Ah! See? It's this place!
That person lives here!
I knew it!
- Right.
- What?
No one’s here right now.
Yeah.
Huh?
A tortoise?
Huh.
When the rugosa roses
Bloom
On the Cape of Shiretoko…
Hotaru.
Will you play for me?
I can't play the guitar.
Just give it a try.
You don't have to be perfect.
Sorry,
I'd like to have a talk with Saku.
- Oh, welcome back.
- I'm back.
Hotaru's got more talent than you do.
Maybe so.
Hey, I heard you two
are getting along nicely?
Hotaru has told me all about it.
That’s how I see it.
Come on.
Tell me about it!
I'll use it as material.
What material?
I’m thinking of drawing it myself.
A boys' love manga.
Please don't.
It's going to be my posthumous work!
Really now…
You’re always such a spoilsport!
Never mind.
I'll tell you.
I'll tell you anything.
Anything, huh?
Is there anything else I can do?
Not really.
There’s nothing, really!
In that case, I'll sing.
- I’ll sing, so just listen.
- Huh?
Let’s start over.
Huh?
This time,
I’ll seriously think about
how we can stay together.
HOME FOR SALE
- Sorry.
- Huh?
I went with Hatano to file
our partnership registration,
and we plan to buy a house together.
You're really in love…
with that guy, huh?
I'm not sure if it's love or not,
be it a "clamp"
or "love and revolution"…
But I thought maybe
I could believe in that.
That just means you're
head over heels for him.
We’ll be happy our way,
so you do your thing and be happy too.
This isn't your happy ending, right?
- What's my happy ending?
- I don't know.
After playing the 5th fret,
press the 3rd fret.
Repeat the sequence three times.
That's it.
Your son will sing now.
"The Tortoise Song".
Ready, set, go!
Snail-y, snail-y, slow and steady
Tip-tap, tip-tap, ready, ready
Sloshy, sloshy, wiggly feet
Scurry, scurry, tiny beat
Walking slow but feeling strong
Gonna live a life so long
Snail-y, snail-y, shell so tough
Tip-tap, tip-tap, slow but rough
Sloshy, sloshy, wiggly feet
Scurry, scurry, tiny beat
Shell is hard, I’m feeling proud
Gonna live long, shout it loud
Snail-y, snail-y, stretch my neck
Tip-tap, tip-tap, what the heck
Sloshy, sloshy, wiggly feet
Scurry, scurry, tiny beat
Stretch my neck, I'm feeling fine
Gonna live a long, long time
Where am I? Oh, look around
What a lovely place I've found
You did well, Hotaru.
"It’s scary to put into words.
Because I didn’t believe
in a happy ending.
But I…
met you.
I love you.
Together, surely…"
"Finally…
you said it."
THREE STEPS TO A HAPPY ENDING
Where's the convenience store?
- I'd like to go there.
- Okay.
Is it this way?
Do you need something?
I found a tortoise.
Ah! Okay.
- Please head this way.
- Okay.
GUARDING SMILES & PEACE OF MIND
RECRUITING POLICE OFFICERS
Are you sure you can go home by yourself?
Yes, I'm sure.
Really?
Yes. I'm fine by myself from here.
Thank you.
I thought you were prepared for it, no?
I was, but…
No need to worry.
I’ll be in touch with you again.
Oh, last thing.
Can you just say this line here
for me?
No.
Spoilsport.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry…
for everything.
Your mom…
is really happy now, you know?
Okay then.
Good luck.
See you.
I have something to announce.
Okay.
We’re officially partners now.
PARTNERSHIP REGISTRATION CARD
Uh…
Congratulations.
Since you’ve helped so much,
I thought we'd let you know.
Yeah.
About what's going forward…
Yes?
…I'll continue to act as your parent.
You can plan your future, and everything
beyond it, with peace of mind.
Whatever you decide,
Hatano and I have agreed to cooperate.
And, of course, as your teacher,
I’ll support you too.
- So, you’re not spending the 30 million?
- Nope.
You'd be violating the contract.
Are you sure about this?
If it wasn't for you, Hotaru, we probably
wouldn’t have become partners.
Me and Sakuta, that is.
So, thank you.
I hope we can continue from here on out.
Yes, please.
Alright, let’s decide
on your career path then.
- Already?
- What are you talking about?
The parent-teacher meeting
was two months ago!
- Right.
- Um…
I also have something to announce.
What is it?
I found…
what I love and what I want to do freely.
And that is?
The guitar.
I love guitars.
Really?
I don't know why, but I'm happy about it.
Oh wow. What do we do,
- Sakuta?
- You're way too excited.
If you'd like,
I can teach you anytime,
as much as you want.
I don't mean the playing part.
- What?
- Huh?
I mean the making part.
I want to make guitars.
So, until my mom comes back,
I’ll be in your care.
After the beep tone,
please leave your name and message.
Hello, Mom?
I found something I love.
But it’s a little scary.
When I have things I love,
people who matter to me,
or my own happiness,
I keep thinking about
what would happen if I lost them.
- Let’s eat together.
- Yeah!
EGGS
How about this property then?
What do you think of here?
This condo here…
I’m here today to look for a house
for my own sake.
Still, I’m going to try my best
to believe…
in myself,
in my feelings for what I love,
in the kind words I’ve received,
in the people who are by my side…
PARTY B & C WILL SUPPORT PARTY A’S DREAM
…and of course, you too, Mom.
Two more left.
NAGANO PREFECTURE
Talk to you soon. Bye.
Sorry for the wait.
- Ah, thank you.
- Please enjoy.
Doesn't this place look nice?
It has big windows too.
It faces west, though.
Life is going to be hell
in the late afternoons.
Is that right?
How about this one?
Which one?
I forgot you have poor eyesight.
It’s just the text is small.
Wait, this one is amazing!
Huh?
You’ll die one day too, right, Hatano?
I love you, Hatano.
You finally said it.
INOKASHIRA APARTMENTS
TOKYO METROPOLITAN POLICE DEPARTMENT
Subtitle translation by: Jeffery